And let's get started with the AI detector.
So I think it can look so cool, right?
To check if this text is generated by AR or not, you know,
it's a very important question actually.
No one knows the answer.
I don't do you.
Okay, whatever.
So as you see, we can also upload a document
or we can paste the text over here,
just doing that.
We'll be okay.
As you see, we have a list of languages
that we can use Quilbot on,
a French, Spanish, German, et cetera.
And I right click and I click paste
to see what we have.
So I click detect AI.
It's 1,442 words and let's see the result.
So as you see, 96% of text is likely AI.
96% is AI generated.
0% is human written.
And AI refine and 4% is human written.
Okay, thank you so much for the 4%, you know.
It means a lot.
It means a lot of chat GPT.
Thank you so much.
But whatever.